phonearea.net 2009-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Blogatize Blog Network

LAST UPDATED: 5/18/2009

Blogatize.net and its related Weblogs always respects the privacy of its visitors and endeavors to protect their privacy while browsing their collective Websites and Weblogs. Blogatize has created the following Privacy Policy in order to establish clear guidelines that govern the collection, storage, use and disclosure of personal and non-personal information of its visitors and users.

  * Collection of Personally Identifiable Information
  * Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information
  * Protection of Visitors' Personally Identifiable Information
  * Collecting Anonymous Non-Personally Identifiable Information
  * Collecting Cookie-Based Information
  * Related Websites and Weblogs
  * Visitors' Consent

Blogatize.net never automatically collects personally identifiable information such as name, address, phone number, email id and so on, from its visitors. From time to time, though, Blogatize will collect such information voluntarily offered by its visitors, by filling out various forms, such as subscribing to newsletters, filling contest entry forms and so on. Blogatize only collects such information for the purpose of responding to visitors and keep up communication with them. Blogatize will only use personally identifiable information after having gained the express permission from the user to do so.

In case visitors no longer wish to receive emails or further correspondence from Blogatize.net, they only need to follow the unsubscribe instructions to remove themselves from the mailing distribution list. The personal information collected in such cases is never revealed to any third party or company in the future.

Blogatize.net may choose to disclose personally identifiable information of visitors, to third parties, using aggregated, completely anonymous and non-personally identifiable methods. This is done only for marketing and advertising research purposes, in order to study and understand consumer behavior better, also to offer visitors a better browsing experience on Blogatize and other related Websites.

Visitors should make sure to exercise caution while disclosing personally identifiable information while logging onto chat rooms, bulletin boards and while commenting on the Weblogs contained within Blogatize. These are public areas that can be accessed by anyone, so visitors may run the risk of receiving unsolicited messages, spam mails and so on from unscrupulous third parties.

Blogatize.net always strives to protect its visitors' personally identifiable information, by using advanced technology such as firewalls, secure, password-protected servers and so on. Access of such personal information on Blogatize.net is limited only to authorized personnel. Blogatize retains this personally identifiable information only as long as required by the Website or by the law. Blogatize immediately deletes this information or makes it anonymous once it stops being necessary to store the same.

Blogatize.net automatically collects anonymous, non-personally identifiable information when any visitor logs into the Website or uses any of its services. Such information includes the date, time and length of the visit to Blogatize and its related Weblogs, logs of page views, the type of browser and Operating System used by the visitor and the domain name of the visitor's Internet Service Provider. Blogatize.net collects such visitor information only to study user behavior and offer tailor-made solutions to the visitors in the future. Blogatize may also share this anonymous, non-personally identifiable information with other parties, such as advertisers, sponsors, partners and broadcasters.

"Cookies" are snippets of information that a Website transfers to a visitor's hard drive, in order to keep a record for future identification purposes. Cookies also help the visitor save his/her passwords, preferences, settings and so on, thereby enabling them to browse quickly through the Website each time. Blogatize.net may use cookies on its Websites. Blogatize, however, does not use these cookies to collect personal information, except in reference to password-protecting visitors' online registration and so on. Visitors may, at any time, choose to turn off cookie-collection by Blogatize in order to avoid the collection of such cookie-based information.

Blogatize.net may contain links to several other Websites and Weblogs. These do not come under the purview of Blogatize and so, will follow their own Privacy Policy. Visitors should read through these and understand them well before opting to reveal their personally identifiable information to such third parties. Blogatize.net may not be held liable for any of the policies, procedures or activities on third party websites linked to its Website or related Weblogs.

By using the services offered on Blogatize.net, you agree to abide by the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. Kindly refrain from using Blogatize or provide your personal information if you are not in agreement of the above.
